http://www.irish-cookery-school.com/privacy/

Privacy Policy
We are committed to ensuring the best standards of practice in all our activities. Visitors to our website can be assured that the protection of privacy and confidentiality are given the highest priority. All personal information is collected, held and used in strict compliance with the Data Protection Act 1998.
Information Collected
We do not collect any personal information from visitors to our website other than information that is knowingly and voluntarily given. Anonymous information is collected, such as the number of visitors to the website in a given period or details of properties and dates selected for online bookings, but it is purely statistical and cannot be used to identify an individual user. Cookies are not used to collect any other information from visitors to the website. Visitors interested in requesting more information can provide contact details via a fill-in form. Visitors cannot be contacted unless such information is given. Visitors are also invited to give additional company information but a decision not to do so does not affect any subsequent negotiations or discussions.
Use of Information
The information collected will be used to contact you with further details of our current activities or to send details of future initiatives or events. It may also be used for research purposes. You can inform us at any time if you no longer require such information to be sent.
If you provide your email address to us, you agree that we may send information to you by email in relation to our Services and in relation to any new services, initiatives or events. You will have the opportunity to unsubscribe from any such emails at any time.
We will share your details with our booking system, SuperControl for the purpose of them delivering their service to us. For example, they provide a verified reviews service called UpFrontReviews and we may ask them to send you an email invitation to submit a review about your stay. We will NEVER sell your details to any third party. You consent to us providing your details to SuperControl in this way. You will have the opportunity to unsubscribe from any such emails at any time.
Data Security
We take appropriate measures to safeguard the information we hold from unauthorised access or improper use. Our database is stored in a secure, password protected location. Only users authorised by us have access to this data.
Integrity of Data
We take all reasonable measures to ensure that the information we hold is accurate. In particular, we use reliable collection methods and destroy or convert to an anonymous form, any out-of-date data. Individuals may request details of all personal information held by us so as to contest inaccurate or incomplete data, verify the information and have it corrected as appropriate.
Children
Our website is not targeted at children but in any event personal information will not knowingly be collected from children under fourteen years without parental consent.
Enforcement
Any queries relating to our collection or use of personal information should be addressed to info@belle-isle.com.
Newsletter Sign Up
Be the first to hear about our latest news and special offers.Name*
First
Last
Email
Privacy Policy*Please tick to consent to your data being stored and for us to respond in line with the guidelines set out in our Privacy Policy
Belle isle Estate and Private Island, Lisbellaw, Enniskillen, BT94 5HG, +44 (0) 286 638 7231
© Belle Isle Estate, 2020
